[{"id":619,"question":"How can we access the data sent through the URL with the POST method?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$_POST[\"var\"];","answer_b":"$_REQUEST[\"var\"];","answer_c":"$_GET[\"var\"];","answer_d":"$_PUT[\"var\"];","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":145,"question":"Block elements are normally displayed without starting a new line.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":328,"question":"Which of the following statements are true?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Names of databases, tables and columns can be up to 64 characters in length","answer_b":"Alias names can be up to 255 characters in length","answer_c":"Names of databases, tables and columns can be up to 256 characters in length","answer_d":"Alias names can be up to 64 characters in length","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":889,"question":"If you exit a container accidentally, will you lose all the work?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":823,"question":"BASH stands for:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Bourne Again SHell","answer_b":"BAsic SHell","answer_c":"Basic Async SHell","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":917,"question":"How to define a service without a selector?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Specify the external name","answer_b":"Specify an endpoint with IP","answer_c":"Address and port Just by specifying the IP address","answer_d":"Specifying the label and api-version","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":162,"question":"Which HTML element is used to specify a header for a document or section?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<top>","answer_b":"<header>","answer_c":"<head>","answer_d":"<section>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":539,"question":"How can we define a Video Tag in HTML 5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<video src \"URL\"><\/video>","answer_b":"<video src=\"URL\"><\/video>","answer_c":"<video><\/video>","answer_d":"<video src:\"URL\"><\/video>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":837,"question":"Docker Toolbox is an installer for quick setup and launch of a Docker environment on Mac and Windows systems. Select all of the Docker tools that come with the Docket Toolbox","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Docker Machine for running docker-machine commands","answer_b":"Oracle VirtualBox","answer_c":"A shell pre-configured for a Docker command-line environment","answer_d":"Docker Compose for running the docker-compose commands","answer_e":"A shell post-configured for a Docker command-line environment","answer_f":"Oracle RealBox Containers"},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":909,"question":"_________ service is automatically created for you K8s cluster creation and takes care of the internal routing of the cluster.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"NodePort","answer_b":"Load Balancer","answer_c":"Headless","answer_d":"ClusterIP","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":955,"question":"How to list all pods that are either labelled with env=development or with env=production","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$ kubectl get pods -l 'env in (production, development)'","answer_b":"$ kubectl get pods 'env in (production, development)'","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":365,"question":"The ASC and DESC keywords can be used in the same statement","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":582,"question":"Can I run several versions of PHP at the same time?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":1018,"question":"Which Process Validates And Configures Data For The Api Objects Like Pods, Services?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kube-apiserver process validates and configures data for the api objects.","answer_b":"kube-apiserver process validates and configures data for the gui objects.","answer_c":"kube-apiserver process validates and configures data for the cli objects.","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":116,"question":"Which of the following is used to declare a constant","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"const","answer_b":"define","answer_c":"constant","answer_d":"def","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":634,"question":"How is the comparison of objects done in PHP?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"We use the operator '===' to test two objects are instanced from the same class and have same attributes and equal values.","answer_b":"We use the operator '=' to test two objects are instanced from the same class and have same attributes and equal values.","answer_c":"We use the operator '==' to test two objects are instanced from the same class and have same attributes and equal values.","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":645,"question":"How can we find the process name from its process id? Assume the Proccess ID is 1","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ps \u2013p 1","answer_b":"find 1","answer_c":"top 1","answer_d":"get 1","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":684,"question":"What is the default value of UMASK?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"022","answer_b":"044","answer_c":"777","answer_d":"222","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"},{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":534,"question":"The _____ character tells browsers to stop tagging the text","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"?","answer_b":">","answer_c":"%","answer_d":"\/","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":422,"question":"Is the NULL value treated as 0?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"}]